Guide to the Cornell University Glee Club Records, 1884-2014
Cornell University Glee Club Records, 1884-2014
- Series VII. Other materials
  - Subseries B. Posters and Fliers
    - Germany Tour Concert at the 24th Infantry Division, June 7 (Map-case 1)
    - Fiestas de Navidad y Reyes concert, January 4, 1992 (Map-case 1)
    - Requiem Smith College/Cornell University Glee Club (Map-case 1)
  - Subseries C. Sheet Music
    - Cornell Reunion Song, 1916 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Carnelian and White, 1906 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - My Old Cornell, 1917 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Fight for Cornell, 1907 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Cornell I Yell Cornell, 1909 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Subseries D. Glee, Banjo and Mandolin Club Programs1884-1959
    - Programs, 1884-1889 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Programs, 1890-1894 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Programs, copy of photograph of Glee Club in 1895, 1895-1899 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Programs, 1900-1909 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Programs, Glee Club Songs, "March on Cornell", 1910-1914 (Box 19, Folder 5)
      Written by Hollis Dann
    - Programs, "The Pagent", 1915-1919 (Box 19, Folder 6)
      Program for The Women of the University
    - Programs, 1920 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Programs, 1921-1924 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Progams, Luggage Tags, Tour Handbook, 1925-1929 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Programs, Tour Handbook, 1930-1939 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Programs, Member Handbook, Tour Handbooks, 1940-1949 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Programs, Tour Handbooks, 1950-1951 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Programs, Undated (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Programs, 1952 (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Programs, 1953-1955 (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - Programs, 1956-1959 (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Programs, European Tour Handbook, Articles, 1960-1962 (Box 19, Folder 17)
      Including Ithaca Journal Centerfold describing Glee Club 1960 trip to Russia, Cornell Daily Sun article
    - Programs, newspaper clipping, 1963 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Programs, invitation, centennial, convocation, 1964-1965 (Box 20, Folder 2)
      Includes Cornell Club letter to invite Cornellians to a Gala Dinner Revolving around their stop in Chicago
    - Programs, invitations, Cornell Latin American Year, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 3)
      Includes invitation to a reception from the Ambassator to the United States in Manila in honor of the Cornell Glee Club
    - Programs, publicity booklet, 1967-1968 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Programs, 1969-1970 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Programs, invitations, 1971-1974 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Programs, invitations, 1975-1979 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Programs, invitations, 1979-1980 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Programs, invitations, Endowment Campaign Booklet, 1981-1983 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Programs, invitations, 1984-1987 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Programs, invitations, China tour handbook, 1988-1989 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Programs, tour handbook, member handbook, 1990-1991 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Programs, 1992-1993 (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Programs, tour handbook, 1994-2000 (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - Programs, booklets, tour handbooks, 2001-2004 (Box 21, Folder 27)
    - Programs, invitations, tour handbook, 2005-2011 (Box 21, Folder 28)
      Including an invitation for the Glee Club to sing in the California Capital Rotunda on their 2011 California Tour
    - Programs, invitations, 2012-2014 (Box 21, Folder 29)